weasyl.com 2015-03-19

# Privacy Policy — Weasyl

Weasyl.com takes your privacy very seriously. To make sure your personal information is secure, we communicate our privacy and security guidelines to Weasyl staff and employees and strictly enforce privacy safeguards within the company. This Privacy Policy applies to our web site, Weasyl.com. This Privacy Policy explains what information we collect through the Site, how we use that information, and what choices you have.

Weasyl contains links to other web sites. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of any companies or individuals that Weasyl does not control, or any web sites that you link to from Weasyl. You should use caution and review the privacy policies of any sites that you visit from ours to learn more about their information practices.

Please take a few moments to read this agreement. By accessing Weasyl, you agree to accept the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and are aware that our policies may evolve in the future as indicated below.

#### What we may collect:

In various places on Weasyl, we collect “Personally Identifiable Information,” such as your name, age, gender, postal address, telephone number, e-mail address, credit card information, or other information that can be used to contact you or identify you as an individual. For example, we collect this information when you register for membership, subscribe for a paid account, sign up for e-mail newsletters and purchase products or services. From time to time in the future we may offer additional features, services, and promotional opportunities that would require you to submit Personally Identifiable Information to participate.

When sending a gift to another user or non-user, you may also be required to supply their name, mailing address, e-mail address and phone number.

We also collect “Anonymous Information” such as your IP address, the type of browser you use, the pages on our Sites that you have visited, and the advertisements that you have clicked on. Your Personally Identifiable Information is not linked to your Anonymous Information.

We do not intend that children will use the site. We do not solicit or knowingly collect information from children under 13 years of age, nor will we accept registration from them. If we learn that we have inadvertently collected information from any individual(s) under 13 years of age, we will expunge the information from our records and databases as quickly as possible.

#### Access To and Retention of Personal Information

Weasyl makes it easy for you to keep your personal information accurate, complete, and up to date. We will retain your personal information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.

You can help ensure that your contact information and preferences are accurate, complete, and up to date by logging in to your account at www.weasyl.com.

For other personal information, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access so you can request that we correct the data if it is inaccurate or delete the data if Weasyl is not required to retain it by law or for legitimate business purposes. We may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, are extremely impractical, or for which access is not otherwise required by local law. Access, correction, or deletion requests can be made by contacting us at [privacy@weasyl.com](mailto:privacy@weasyl.com).

#### How your personal information is used:

We use Personally Identifiable Information that you provide to communicate with you, to process orders for products and services, to customize advertising and content available on Weasyl, to conduct research for internal purposes and to use such information to improve our services and Weasyl itself.

If you so choose, we will also use it to send you information about products and services that may be of interest to you. Later on in this Privacy Policy, we provide you with more information on what choices you have. We will also send you important notices regarding policy changes, purchases and conditions.

We use information that is not personally identifiable to determine how people use our web site and its services. For example this data tells us information including how often users click on our advertisements, which files are downloaded most frequently, and which areas of our site are the most popular. Analyzing this data allows us to improve the offerings on and performance of our site(s).

#### Collection and Use of Non-Personal Information

Weasyl may collect Non-Personal Information about its users. Non-Personal Information is data in a form that does not permit direct association with any specific individual. Examples of this includes:

  1. Occupation
  2. Language
  3. Zip code
  4. Area code
  5. Unique device identifier
  6. Location

If combined with Personal information, all the information will be treated as personal for as long as it remains combined.

#### Protection of Personal Information

Weasyl takes precautions — including administrative, technical, and physical measures — to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.

Weasyl online services use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption on all web pages where personal information is collected. To make purchases from these services, you must use an SSL-enabled browser such as Safari, Firefox, Google Chrome, Opera and Internet Explorer. Doing so protects the confidentiality of your personal information while it is transmitted over the Internet.

When you use some Weasyl products, services, or applications or post on a Weasyl forum, chat room, or social networking service, the personal information you share is visible to other users and can be read, collected, or used by them. You are responsible for the personal information you choose to submit in these instances. For example, if you list your name and email address in a forum posting, that information is public. Please take care when using these features.

#### Cookies and Other Technologies

A browser cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer which may be read by the website each time the visitor returns. We use cookies on our website in order to establish and maintain the session identity of signed in users, track the preferences of users with regards to the website interface, and otherwise operate our website and its features.

Users who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their web browser to refuse cookies before accessing our website; however, doing so may prevent certain features of our website from functioning properly or as prescribed.

The website, online services, interactive applications, email messages, advertisements may also use other technologies such as pixel tabs and web beacons. These technologies help us better understand user behavior, tell us which parts of our website people have visited, and facilitate and measure the effectiveness of advertisements and web searches. We treat information collected by cookies and other technologies as non-personal information. However, to the extent that Internet Protocol (IP) addresses or similar identifiers are considered personal information by local law, we also treat these identifiers as personal information. Similarly, to the extent that non-personal information is combined with personal information, we treat the combined information as personal information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy.

We gather some information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type and language, Internet service provider (ISP), referring and exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information to understand and analyze trends, to administer the site, to learn about user behavior on the site, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may use this information in our marketing and advertising services.

In some of our email messages, we may use a “click-through URL” linked to content on the Weasyl website. When customers click one of these URLs, they pass through a separate web server before arriving at the destination page on our website. We track this click-through data to help us determine interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of our customer communications. If you prefer not to be tracked in this way, you should not click text or graphic links in the email messages.

Pixel tags enable us to send email messages in a format customers can read, and they tell us whether mail has been opened. We may use this information to reduce or eliminate messages sent to customers.

#### Disclosure to Third Parties

At times we may make certain personal information available to strategic partners that work with Weasyl to provide products and services, or that help Weasyl market to customers.

_Service Providers_

Weasyl shares personal information with companies who provide services such as information processing, fulfilling customer orders, delivering products to you, managing and enhancing customer data, providing customer service, assessing your interest in our products and services, and conducting customer research or satisfaction surveys. These companies are obligated to protect your information and may be located wherever Weasyl operates.

_Others_

It may be necessary − by law, legal process, litigation, and/or requests from public and governmental authorities within or outside your country of residence − for Weasyl to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that for purposes of national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary or appropriate.

We may also disclose information about you if we determine that disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce our terms and conditions or protect our operations or users. Additionally, in the event of a reorganization, merger, or sale we may transfer any and all personal information we collect to the relevant third party.

#### International Users

Information you provide may be transferred or accessed by entities around the world as described in this Privacy Policy. Weasyl abides by the “safe harbor” frameworks set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information collected by organizations in the European Economic Area and Switzerland. Learn more about the U.S. Department of Commerce Safe Harbor Program.

#### Privacy Questions

If you have any questions or concerns about Weasyl's Privacy Policy or data processing, please contact us at [privacy@weasyl.com](mailto:privacy@weasyl.com).

Weasyl may update its Privacy Policy from time to time. When we change the policy in a material way, a notice will be posted on our website along with the updated Privacy Policy. We will also notify registered users by sending a notification to their registered email.
